Guide to the K. Leroy Irvis Papers, 1946-1995 AIS.1971.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Awards, Realia, Etc., 1936-2006; XVII.
  - Awards, Degrees, and Honors (2010 Addition), 1938-2006; 2.
    - 1985-2003 (Box 148)
      Distinguished Leadership and Service (Cheyney University), 1993
      Honorary Doctor of Laws (Beaver College), 1999
      International Year of the Older Persons, 1999
      Resolution (City of Pittsburgh), 1995
      Distinguished Service to the Commonwealth (Speaker of the House), 2005
      Thank You (K. Leroy Irvis Towers Tennant Council), 2003
    - 1954-2002 (Box 149)
      Inaugural Honoree (Crawford McDonald Greene Providing of Excellence Award), 2002
      Distinguished Professor (Univ. of Pitt School of Social Work Black Action Society), 2002
      Outstanding Achievements (Mon Valley Branch NAACP), undated
      Service for the Mentally Retarded (PA Assoc. for Retarded Children), undated
      Service Award (SUNY Albany Alumni Assoc), undated
      Distinguished Alumni (SUNY), 1969
      Honorary Assoc. of Arts Degree (CCAC), 1995
      Support of Higher Ed (CCAC), 1988
      Honorary Membership (Vanguard Jaycees), 1979
      Staff Member (University of Pittsburgh School of Law, Law Review), 1954
      Life Member (NAACP), 1978
      Daffodil Day (American Cancer Society), 1986
      Outstanding Leadership (Black Conference on Higher Education), 1985
      City of Philadelphia Citation, Cathryn Irvis, 1983
      Honorary Doctor of Laws (Moravian College), 1991
    - 1996-2004 (Box 150)
      Lifetime Achievement Award (Democratic Party of Allegheny County), 2004
      Distinguished Alumni (University of Pittsburgh School of Law), 2004
      Good Government Award (League of Women Voters of Greater Pgh), 2000
      Lifelong Service (African-American Students Scholastic Awards CCAC), 1996
    - 1938-2004
      - SUNY Albany Degree, 1938 (Box 151, Folder 1)
      - SUNY Albany Degree, 1939 (Box 151, Folder 2)
      - Certificate of Merit (Pittsburgh Club of the National Association of Negro Business and Professional Women's Clubs), 1972 (Box 151, Folder 3)
      - Commendation (Students Concerned with Public Health), 1972 (Box 151, Folder 4)
      - Resolution (Port Authority of Allegheny County), 1973 (Box 151, Folder 5)
      - Certificate of Award for Neighborhood Pride (Cliff Cass at Block Club), 1976 (Box 151, Folder 6)
      - Certificate of Recognition (ACT 101 Programs), 1977 (Box 151, Folder 7)
      - Honorary Member (Pittsburgh Black Theatre Dance Ensemble Corporation), 1977 (Box 151, Folder 8)
      - Outstanding Public Service (Western Pennsylvania Black Political Assembly), 1977 (Box 151, Folder 9)
      - Honorary Doctor of Laws (Lincoln University), 1979 (Box 151, Folder 10)
      - Outstanding Achievement (Pennsylvania Black Political Assembly), 1979 (Box 151, Folder 11)
      - Pittsburgh's 1st Blacks in Business and Professions Award (Pittsburgh Club of the National Association of Negro Business and Professional Women's Clubs), 1979 (Box 151, Folder 12)
      - Participation on Dedication Ceremony (Developers of KLI Towers), 1980 (Box 151, Folder 13)
      - Certificate of Appreciation (Indiana University of Pennsylvania), 1981 (Box 151, Folder 14)
      - Who's Who in the World (Marquis Publications Board), 1980-1981 (Box 151, Folder 15)
      - Recognition (Young Democrats of Allegheny County), 1982 (Box 151, Folder 16)
      - Outstanding Achievement Award (Abraxas Foundation), 1983 (Box 151, Folder 17)
      - Certificate of Appreciation (Harrisburg Jaycees), 1983 (Box 151, Folder 18)
      - Citation (Cheyney University of Pennsylvania), 1984 (Box 151, Folder 19)
      - Certificate of Appreciation (Urban League of Metropolitan Harrisburg), 1985 (Box 151, Folder 20)
      - Appreciation (Bryn Mawr Road), 1986 (Box 151, Folder 21)
      - Acknowledgement (Hands Across America), 1986 (Box 151, Folder 22)
      - K. Leroy Irvis Day (Allegheny Board of Commissioners), 1986 (Box 151, Folder 23)
      - Legislator Award (Pennsylvania Citizens for Better Libraries), 1987 (Box 151, Folder 24)
      - Best Model Plane Builder of the Year (AMA), 1988 (Box 151, Folder 25)
      - Honorary Degree (Harrisburg Area Community College), 1988 (Box 151, Folder 26)
      - Certificate of Appreciation (Langley High School), 1988 (Box 151, Folder 27)
      - Honorary Degree (Moravian College), 1989 (Box 151, Folder 28)
      - Trustee Recognition (University of Pittsburgh), 1989 (Box 151, Folder 29)
      - President's Award (Lincoln University), 1992 (Box 151, Folder 30)
      - Honorary Citizenship (Erie), 1993 (Box 151, Folder 31)
      - Resolution (Pennsylvania Historical and Museum Commission), 1993 (Box 151, Folder 32)
      - Citation (Pennsylvania House of Representatives), 1993 (Box 151, Folder 33)
      - Citation (Pennsylvania Legislative Black Caucus), 1993 (Box 151, Folder 34)
      - Certificate of Award for Service to Community (Ebenezer Baptist Church), 1995 (Box 151, Folder 35)
      - Resolution (Pittsburgh City Council), 1995 (Box 151, Folder 36)
      - Honorary Degree (Community College of Allegheny County), 1997 (Box 151, Folder 37)
      - Citation (Pennsylvania House of Representatives), 1997 (Box 151, Folder 38)
      - Pennsylvania Founder's Award (Pennsylvania Historical and Museum Commission), 1998 (Box 151, Folder 39)
      - Resolution 384 (Pennsylvania House of Representatives), 1998 (Box 151, Folder 40)
      - Community Citation of Merit (Allegheny County), 1999 (Box 151, Folder 41)
      - Citation (Pennsylvania House of Representatives), 1999 (Box 151, Folder 42)
      - K. Leroy Irvis Dinner and Awards Banquet (Pennsylvania Senate), 2000 (Box 151, Folder 43)
      - Certificate of Appreciation (Pennsylvania for Adult Literacy), 2000 (Box 151, Folder 44)
      - Citation (Pennsylvania House of Representatives), 2000 (Box 151, Folder 45)
      - Providing Excellence Award (Crawford McDonald Green LLC), 2002 (Box 151, Folder 46)
      - Honorary Degree (Edinboro University of Pennsylvania), 2002 (Box 151, Folder 47)
      - Certificate of Recognition (ACT 101/TIME Program), 2003 (Box 151, Folder 48)
      - Proclamation (Allegheny County), 2004 (Box 151, Folder 49)
      - Congratulations (Pennsylvania Treasurer Barbara Hafer), 2004 (Box 151, Folder 50)
      - Citation (Pennsylvania House of Representatives), 2004 (Box 151, Folder 51)
      - Resolution 555 (Pennsylvania House of Representatives), 2004 (Box 151, Folder 52)
    - 2004-2006
      - Recognition (Pennsylvania Senate), 2004 (Box 152, Folder 1)
      - Byrd R. Brown Civil Rights Award (Office of the Lt. Governor), 2005 (Box 152, Folder 2)
      - Honorary Degree (Clarion University of Pennsylvania), 2005 (Box 152, Folder 3)
      - Speakers Ball, 2005 (Box 152, Folder 4)
      - Condolence Resolution (Pennsylvania Legislative Black Caucus), 2006 (Box 152, Folder 5)
      - Condolence (Pennsylvania Senate), 2006 (Box 152, Folder 6)
      - Resolution 248 (Pennsylvania Senate), 2006 (Box 152, Folder 7)
      - Commemoration (Representative Wheatley, Pennsylvania House of Representatives), 2006 (Box 152, Folder 8)
      - Condolences (198th Legislative District), 2006 (Box 152, Folder 9)
      - Distinguished Political Achievement (Directory of Distinguished Americans), undated (Box 152, Folder 10)
      - Citation (Pennsylvania House of Representatives), undated (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - 1963-1999 (Box 153)
      Creativity in Portraits/Sculpture (MLK Jr. Reading/Culture Center), 1995
      Chairman's Award (Pennsylvania Democratic Party), undated
      Appreciation (20th Anniversary Reception of Community College Act), 1963
      Salute (Central Pennsylvania Committee), 1978
      Outstanding Leadership (Harrisburg NAACP), 1987
      1st Decade Award (DBCERD), 1980
      Appreciation (Bidwell), 1989
      Minority and Majority Caucus Chairman, 1963-1964, 1965-1966
      Honorary PA Artist (PA Council on Aging 3rd Annual Senior Arts Festival), 1988
      Special Achiever (TALKS), 1975
      Stien, KLI with Esteem from Temple University President, undated
      Man of the Year Nominee, 1969-1970
      Annual Civic Award (PA Baptist State Convention, INC), 1975
      Leadership (Business and Professional Assn. of Pgh.), 1975
      Significant Service (Community Release Agency), 1976
      Mellon Legal Writing Program Distinguish Achievement Award, 1993
    - 1975-1988 (Box 154)
      Outstanding Service (United Black Ward Chairman Achiever Award), undated
      Tireless Effort (City of Erie), 1979
      Salute (William Penn Committee), 1977
      OIC State Legislative Award (Opportunities Industrialization), 1984
      President's Award (PA Trial Lawyers Association), 1986
      Contribution (Hill House Association), 1975
      H.J. Heinz Honor, 1988
      Appreciation for H.B. 942 (Commonwealth of PA), 1984
      SUNY Distinguished Alumni Medal
    - 1994-2003 (Box 155)
      Drum Major for Justice Award (Homer S. Brown Law Association), 2001
      Better Life Award (Pennsylvania Health and Welfare Committee), 1994
      Excellence in Leadership (Dominion), 2003
      Frederick D. Patterson Community Leadership Award (United Negro College Fund), 1995
      Distinguished Pitt Alumnus, 2001-2002
    - 1969-1989 (Box 156)
      Dr. Martin Luther King Citizen Award (Music & Arts of Pgh), 1969
      Black Trailblazer (Renaissance Too Magazine), 1989
      African American Elected Official (Compliments of Bill Robinson)
      Appreciation for Establishing the Black Conference on Higher Ed, 1973
    - 1981-1986 (Box 157)
      Initiation Kappa Delta Pi, undated
      Appreciation Award (Pennsylvania Health Care Association), 1986
      Award of Excellence (Black Democrats Association of Erie County), 1981
    - 1982 (Box 158)
      Pittsburgh Branch NAACP, 1982
    - 1973-1984 (Box 159)
      Man of the Year (Vanguard Jaycees), 1973
      Masonic Achievement Award (Seventh Masonic District), 1984
    - 1967-1986 (Box 160)
      Delegate at Large to the Democratic National Convention, 1968
      Honorary Member (Association for Bridge Construction and Design), 1976
      Who's Who in America (Marquis Publications Board), 1980/1981
      Honorary Member (Pennsylvania State Mayors Association of First Class Boroughs), 1973
      Harambee (Black Solidarity Fair), 1975
      Certificate of Recognition (Good Hope Baptist Church), 1968
      Certificate of Honor (Metropolitan Tenants Organization), 1970
      Award of Honor (Pennsylvania State Council of Public Employees), 1961
      Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 19th Leg. District), 1974
      Certificate of Appointment (Advisory Committee on Probation), 1975
      Certificate of Merit (City of Erie), 1971
      Resolution (Missouri River Tour), 1976
      Delegate to the Constitutional Convention, 1967-1968
      Certificate of Election (Speaker of the House), 1983
      Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 19th Leg. District), 1986
      Certificate of Election (Democratic Leader of the House), 1981
      Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 19th Leg. District), 1983
    - 1958-2003 (Box 161)
      Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 19th Leg. District PA), 1966
      Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 1st Leg. District Allegheny), 1960
      Resolution (City Council of Harrisburg), 1985
      Honorary Citizenship (New Orleans), 1980
      Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 19th Leg. District), 1973
      Certificate of Election (Minority Whip), 1973
      Certificate of Election (Minority leader of the House), 1971
      Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 19th Leg. District), 1976
      Proclamation (City of Cleveland), 2003
      Resolution of Recognition (City of Cleveland), 2003
      Citation (Pennsylvania Capitol Preservation Committee, 1986
      Proclamation (Office of the Governor), 1987
      Honorary Degree Congratulations from the Governor and Senator (Harrisburg Area Community College), 1988
      National Science Honor Society (Pi Gamma Mu), 1938
      Hall of Fame Award (Afna Education and Research Fund), 1984
      Congratulations (Council of the City of Cleveland), 2003
      Citation (County of Erie), 1993
      Phi Delta Phi Initiation (International Legal Fraternity), 1952
      Member (the Order of the Coif), 1954
      Bachelor of Laws (University of Pittsburgh), 1964
      Juris Doctor (University of Pittsburgh), 1968
      Honorary Doctor of Public Service (Edinboro University of Pennsylvania), 2002
      Attorney and Counselor (Supreme Court of Pennsylvania), 1977
      Congratulations (Catherine Baker Knoll, Treasurer), 1995
      Tribute (Pennsylvania Legal Services Center), 1982
      Certificate of Merit (Pennsylvania Library Association), 1986
      William S. Howell/Charlie Highgate Community Service Award (the Kay Boys Club), 1973
      Certificate of Merit (Edinboro State College), 1971
      Citation (City of Philadelphia), 1977
      Recognition (Admirals Club), 1970
      the Pennsylvania Award (Commonwealth Relations Council of the University of PA), undated
      Distinguished Service Award (Pennsylvania Department of Veteran Affairs), 1967
      Torch of Liberty Award (Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith), 1969
      Resolution 27 (NAACP)
      the Presidents Award for Special Services and Outstanding Achievement (Pennsylvania Teenage Democrats), 1968
      the John Carter Robinson Merit Award (the Western Pennsylvania Research and Historical Society), 1966
      Resolution (Pennsylvania House of Representatives), 1966
      Citizens for the Arts Award Recognition from Dick Thornburgh
      Certificate of Election (Democratic Leader of the House), 1979
      Certificate of Election (19th Legislative District), 1979
      Certificate of Election (Speaker of the House), 1977
      Certificate of Election (Speaker of the House), 1985
      Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 19th Leg. District), 1985
      Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 1st Leg. District), 1958
    - 1980-1986 (Box 162)
      Certificate of Appreciation Kids News Interview (Scenic Hills School), undated
      Center for Studying Social Welfare and Community Development, 1980
      Citizen of the Year (Pennsylvania AFL-CIO), 1986
    - 1980-1984 (Box 163)
      African Episcopal Church Ministerial Alliance of Greater Pittsburgh Award, 1980
      City of Philadelphia Resolution, 1984
    - 1982-1984 (Box 164)
      Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 19th Leg. District), 1984
      Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 19th Leg. District), 1982
    - 1972-1993 (Box 165)
      ARCS Knights of the Order of the Broken Wing, 1993
      The Society of Antique Modelers
      Presidential Award (Harrisburg Branch NAACP), 1972
    - 1977-1987 (Box 166)
      Citation for Distinguished Service (Cheyney State College), 1977
      Certificate of Election (Speaker of the House), 1987
      Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 19th Leg. District), 1987
    - 1965-1969 (Box 167)
      Certificate of Election (Minority Whip of the House), 1967
      Certificate of Election (Majority Leader of the House), 1969
      Certificate of Election (Majority Caucus Chairman of the House), 1965
    - 1963-1965 (Box 168)
      Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 1st Leg. District), 1963
      Certificate of Election (Minority Caucus Chairman), 1963
      Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 7th Leg. District), 1965
    - Certificate of Election (House of Representatives 1st Leg. District Allegheny), 1958 (Box 170)
    - Rev. Jesse Anderson Award for Distinguished Service to Students (Widener University), 1983 (Oversize 199)
    - Statesmen Award (Pennsylvania Legislative Black Caucus), 1985 (Oversize 200)
    - Democracy in Housing Award (Associated Real Estate Brokers of Philadelphia Inc), 1966 (Oversize 201)
    - Distinguished Service Award (Pennsylvania Association of Colleges and Universities), 1990 (Oversize 202)
    - Martin Luther King Citizen Award (Music & Arts of Pittsburgh), 1970 (Oversize 203)
  - Realia (2010 Addition), 1940-2003; 3.
    The material in the Realia subseries was mainly collected by Irvis over the duration of his life. Much of the memorabilia reflects activities or events that he participated in or was honored at. Some of these items include invitations, guest passes, plaques, and medallions. In addition, a large portion of the memorabilia is representative to Irvis' career as a member of the Pennsylvania House of Representatives. These items include, but are not limited to gavels, pins, license plates, and stamps. This subseries has been listed at an itemized level.
    - Scrapbook, 1944-1956 (Box 169)
    - Scrapbook, 1959-1968 (Box 170)
    - Scrapbook, 1961-1981 (Box 171)
    - Scrapbook, 1968-1969 (Box 172)
    - Scrapbook, 1970-1971 (Box 173)
    - Scrapbook, 1973-1988 (Box 174)
    - Scrapbook, 1976-1978 (Box 175)
    - Scrapbook, 1977-1996 (Box 176)
    - Scrapbook, 1978-1979 (Box 177)
    - Scrapbook, 1979 (Box 178)
    - Scrapbook, 1980-1982 (Box 179)
    - 1986-1988 (Box 180)
      Gratitude of Acknowledgement from Quandong College of Education, 1986
      Citation of Cordial Greetings to Quandong College of Education, 1986
      Irvis Retirement News clipping, 1988
    - 1977, 1987 (Box 181)
      Bicentennial Celebration of the U.S. Constitution Signing (Commemorative Invitation), 1987
      Pennsylvania State Legislature News clipping, undated
      Framed Congratulatory Black Socks from Patty and Murray Love, 1977
    - 1961-2003 (Box 182)
      Urban League of Pittsburgh, the Black Family, 2003
      Caricature of Irvis, John Joan Newsroom, 1970
      Early KLI Picture, Johnson and Humphrey Election Poster, 1964
      Tuskegee Airman Poster, signed
      Certificate that Pen was used by Governor to approve H.B. 950, 1965
      Countdown to Eternity (MLK Jr. Photographs) Signed by Author, undated
      Elect Irvis Posters, undated (4)
      Irvis Caricature as Speaker, 1977-1978
      Homer S. Brown Legacy Dinner Award and Caricature, 1986
      Harrisburg Area Community College Commencement Program, 1988
      The Black Chronicle (2)
      Poster sized Portrait of a block long greeting for distinguished lecture at Temple, 1985
      House Bill 430 (Act 341), 1961
    - 1993 (Box 183)
      Commemorative Envelopes and Stamps (U.S. Constitution Bicentennial), 1987
      KLI, Speaker, House of Representatives Parking Sign
    - 1987 (Box 184)
      Commemorative Pamphlet (U.S. Constitution Bicentennial), 1987
      Commemorative Ornament (U.S. Constitution Bicentennial), 1987
    - 1971-1985 (Box 185)
      Inaugural Session Invitation Honoring Irvis as Speaker, 1985-1986
      Italian Ministry of Tourism and Theatre Plaque (Dickinson College), 1985
      Large unmarked gavel
      5th International Conference on Urban Transportation Commemorative Plaque, 1971
      Groundbreaking Ceremony Bidwell Training Center, 1985
      Holiday Wishes from Homeless Children (Philadelphia), 1985
      Congratulatory Telegram from Aaron Levonson (Plaque), 1982
      Letter of Gratitude from Ruth Barton Chairperson of PA Council on Aging (Plaque), 1988
      Letter from Vice President Walter Mondale re: Panama Trip (Framed), 1980
      Wooden Carvings (2 Bowls), undated
    - 1940-1988 (Box 186)
      K. Leroy Irvis, The Speaker, Name Plaques (2), undated
      K. Leroy Irvis, Allegheny County, Name Plaque, undated
      Murray/Irvis Sickle Cell Center Medallion, 1984
      Lake Placid Olympic Medal with Explanatory Note, 1980
      Pin for the Atlanta Democratic National Convention, 1988
      Plastic Pouch "Compliments of K. Leroy Irvis, Speaker..." (2), undated
      Gavel Inscribed with K. Leroy Irvis, Speaker, House of Reps, 1987
      1st Official Continental Congress Bicentennial Commemorative Medal and Cachet, 1974
      Ribbon marked PA House of Reps with KLI Signature and Title, 1985
      Pin, Celebration of Eagles, AMA, 1996
      Mini Flag on Pole "Civil Air Patrol," undated
      Laminated Passes, Rosalynn Carter's Trip to South America, Presidential Guest, 1979
      Model Propeller Blade Carved by Irvis, 1940
      Leftover Piece of a Radio Control Airplane by Irvis, c. 1963
      Loyal Order of the Moose Membership Card for Pat S. Mangino, undated
      Sketch of a Gate on a Wood Block by KLI, undated
      Pen used by Governor Milton Shapp to Approve Senate Bill 74, Dpt on Aging, 1978
      National Conference of State Legislators Name Badge, 1965
      Democratic National Convention, Chicago, 1968
      Wooden Carving, African Head, undated
      Stamps (6)
      Name Badge, Representative KLI, undated
      Name Badge, Majority Leader L. Irvis, undated
      Name Badge, Majority Caucus Chairman, KLI, undated
    - 1945-1993 (Box 187)
      Irvis Coat of Arms
      Support of Drug and Alcohol Abuse Treatment, 1978
      38th DNC New York City, Co-Chair Pin (2), 1980
      Wooden "doodle" of a horse by Irvis, c. 1945
      Pennsylvania Delegation, White House Conference on Aging (Medal), 1981
      House of Representative License Plates (2)
      House of Representatives Voting Switch (Yea or Nay) with note
      DNC Honorary Badge (Delegate), 1976
      DNC Delegate Badge San Francisco, 1984
      17th Constitutional Convention AFL-CIO Honorary Guest Badge, 1976
      Pen gifted from Rachel Lynch, 1993
      Compliments of KLI Stamp
      I Support Irvis Pen
      House of Representatives Minority Whip Pin
      House of Representatives Member Pin, 1979-1980
      House of Representatives Pin, 1979-1980
      House of Representatives Pin, 1977-1978
      House of Representatives Majority Leader Pin, 1977-1978
      House of Representatives Minority Leader Pin, 1979-1980
      House of Representatives Speaker Pin, 1983-1984
      House of Representatives Minority Leader Pin, 1981-1982
      Carved Heads, Gift of Mike Nelson (2), 1990
      K. Leroy Irvis, Speaker, Desk Ornament, 1987
      Pen used to Sign Bill No. 796 by Milton Shapp, 1974
      DNC Citizens Committee NYC Pin, 1980
      Honoree Name Tag Strong Men and Women, undated
      KLI Blank Planner, 1987
      Committee to Elect KLI Kit
      Chipping Chisel used by KLI, 1950
      DNC State Vice Chair Badge, 1980
    - 1988-1990 (Box 188)
      Wooden Bowl Carved by Irvis, 1988
      Hatsepsut, Pharaoh Carved by Irvis, 1990
    - 1987-1988 (Box 189)
      Bookends from the Pennsylvania Chamber of Business and Industry, 1988
      Business Card Holder, undated
      Greater Pittsburgh International Airport Midfield Terminal Groundbreaking, 1987
      University of Pittsburgh Trustee Medal
    - 1977-1986 (Box 190)
      Meet the Mayor Game, 1986
      KLI Stamps (Agreed, See Me, Noted) (3)
      KLI the Speaker, Pen
      Pennsylvania House of Representatives Letter Opener
      House of Representatives Pin, Speaker, 1977-1978
    - 1947-1972 (Box 191)
    - Framed Letter and Portrait of Gerald Ford, 1983 (Oversize 204)
    - Thut-Mose III, carved by Irvis, 1995 (Oversize 205)
    - Oil Painting, "Brotherhood at K. Leroy Irvis Field", undated (Oversize 206)
    - Reading is Fun Poster, Given to Cathy by the Carters during International Year of the Child, 1970 (Oversize 206, Tube 207)
    - Sky Diving Poster, Addressed to Irvis and Signed, 1976 (Oversize 206, Tube 208)
    - Elect Irvis Hand-Painted Poster, undated (Oversize 206, Tube 209)
    - House of Representatives Poster with Irvis Portrait, Proof, undated (Oversize 206, Tube 210)
    - Briefcase, undated (Box 211)
- Publications, 1946-1992; XVIII.
  This series contains a small number of articles written by Irvis as well as media publications and brochures written about his life and work.